and
So let me see how we can do it practically.
Let's open the cobalt strike.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So let's go to the original or some darker band. If you search in telegram for a crack version, you will be getting the cobalt strike. So just click on the mmm, mmm, office macro. So just go to the listener, select the listener. Sorry. Choose. And generate. So let's copy this macro. And first of all, we will do investigative cyber war.
Now let's go for this macro, contains, okay, let's mean go to the sticky notes. No, no, not sticky notes. Let's go for. Okay. Let's go for one notes, if possibly.
So now you can see this generated macro virus. Okay. So here you can see the code. This is the macro virus. And it will be executed through the vbs visual basic setting, VBA visual basics. Right. And you can see some kind of payloads here.
It will be encoded encrypted or strongly obfuscated sometime. So you can see the process run deal 32.exe and run deal 32.exe there. So the threat factors will, I will tell you how the detectors will develop a macro files. So they will go to the board application first.
And they will be choosing template or some of the documents in the contents like this, your salary sleep. This is your current amount, current amount, electricity bill or gas bill water bill or something, something.
And just they will become the macro and view macro. You have to create a new macro. So we are creating a new macro name is Mac. Okay. So just creating a macro name is a Mac. I was creating the macro so you can see here I was replacing the code and I was pasting the code which I have copied from, which I was copied from a cobalt state.
So absolutely from here. So let me install this.
So when I click on the install button, so you can see.
So you can see there is one of the, I got on to virtual. Okay. Let me kill this and I will show. So that session exit.
Let me execute on more time for you. So I just execute her. Okay.
Wait, I can I got a section so you can interrupt and you can query whatever you want like you can I give the PSPS means the process listing process.
So in between we will save this macro we will wait for a result. So file they will go for a file. Save. Okay. So and they will save the document. Save us.
Okay. You can save the document. So but. So if you see.
But if you see this document, this document contains a macro enabled macro executable. So whenever the users opened this document, so the script will be the malicious code.
We, we just have a created a macro, it will be automatically get executed and the, the detector will be getting a connection. So you can see.
So we will be getting a reverse connection from the rendial32.exe. So it was pointed us out. It was like Martha's yellow color. So we'll be getting a reverse connection from the real 32.exe.
So that we will be getting a yellow color in here. So certainly we have seen the code. So there is a rendial32.exe has been executed. So we'll be getting the
reverse connection from rendial32.exe. So let's. So this is the way the detector will hijack your compromised environment. Okay. So when I open the, when I open the board.
I got a second section. So now you can see two sections are here. So if I open the document one more time.
So I'll be getting a third one. Okay. So this is how the detector will hijack your organization by using the phishing attack. Okay. This is a pretty simple way to do. So implementing a phishing.
So let's.
You can see there is nothing here. So the, if the, if any of the user, he, if any of the user, he opened this document, he will not know there is a malicious code will be hidden inside the document.
But yep, we can do a lot of stuff here. Right. So if I send this macro enabled us. So this document to my friends or my families to anyone in any organization, they will be opening this document and the script will be get executed and I will be getting a reversal from that. Okay.
So if you think about the light real words scenario, let me show you something. Okay.
So here you can see in this. So there is a HTM dot HTML file or support dot. But if you, if you import the document in the email, so if the user opened the email, open that word document. So then easily he will be get compromised. So it will be one of a critical attack and it will be very, very, very hard to find what happens inside the environment.
Okay. So I hope you have clear understanding about the fishing. So what the, what the goal will be. So we have did everything in a practical. Yep. We will hop off the studio and we will continue our discussion in the next video. See you guys. Bye bye.